iconsoffright.com 2011-10-05

# Icons Of Fright Private Policy

Please read this notice before using our site. By using the site, you agree to abide by these Terms of Use; please do not use our site if you do not agree with the Terms of Use outlined below. Icons of Fright reserves the right to modify the Terms of Use at its sole discretion, and by using this site, you agree to be bound by the modifications or updates to the Terms of Use. 

**Privacy Notice**

Icons of Fright values your privacy. To keep you informed, we have created this privacy statement that discloses our purposes and methods for online collection and use of information. This statement applies to all information collected through the Icons of Fright website. 

**  
Types of Information Collected**

Generally, personal information is not collected from visitors to Icons of Fright. However, in order to enter contests or register for message boards, personal information is requested.

IF YOU ARE 13 YEARS OF AGE OR YOUNGER you are not allowed to participate in Icons of Fright message boards or contests without parent consent.

**Cookies**

Icons of Fright does not use cookies to collect personal information.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

Icons of Fright does not disclose your personally identifying information to any third parties for any purpose without your prior consent. All reasonable care is taken by staff handling personal information to ensure its security both offline and online.

It's also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on the bulletin board, that information is publicly available and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage the offering of any personally identifying information within the message board itself.

**ICONS OF FRIGHT  DOES NOT, AND WILL NEVER EVER SELL YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS OR PERSONAL INFORMATION.**
